So, in the previous lecture, we learned about the tool calling or function calling capability
of AI agents.
Now, let us go ahead and take a look at the demo.
So, we are already aware that large language models driving AI agents cannot make any
APA calls or integrate with the external systems by themselves.
They can answer only queries based on the generic training data that they have received.
So, in this demo, I am going to show you the micro-cool AI agent that has three key tools.
So, the first tool that it has is the bedrock knowledge basis and through bedrock knowledge
basis, the user can pose any question related to the leave policy based on the HR documents.
So, the next tool that micro-cool AI agent has is the ability to make an API call to an HR
system through which it can check the leave balance based on the particular employee or
employee ID.
Now, through the API call to the HR systems, the end user can check the leave balance
based on his employee ID.
So, that is the second tool.
And then we have the third tool and API call to the hotel site through which the end user
can book a hotel room.
Now, let us take a look at all the three tools, okay.
I have set of questions through which I am going to test out all the tools.
So, the first one is how many paternity leaves are available.
So, let me just copy this.
Now, this is my micro-cool AI agent and if I just click on this edit agent builder and
you can see this is my first tool.
The knowledge basis and leave policy knowledge base.
So, this is my tool one and this is the policy document that it is going to refer to for
any question from the user.
So, I will ask it about the maternity paternity leave and you have two weeks of paid paternity
leave and this is stored in an S3 bucket and then it is enabled through the knowledge
basis.
This is a managed rag base solution from AWS.
So, now, let me just go to this and pose a question.
So, let me just pose a question here.
How many paternity leaves are available and if I just make it full screen and you can
see I got the response here according to the leave policy employees are entitled to two
weeks of paid leave and this is what we had seen here.
Now, if we can just look at the trace, so if we just look at the trace step one and it should
show me here from the raw response, let me check the leave policy for paternity leaves
and then it is saying I have to make a function call and then it is going to this knowledge
base, 6 ending with 6 G and if you just go here and you will see this knowledge base will
end with 6 and you can see here it is ending with 6 G.
Now, let us take a look at the second tool.
Now for the tool 2 and tool 3, I am going to ask the questions which we had asked previously
as well and this time we are going to look at the tool view.
So, let me just pose this question.
So, now we can see the question here book a hotel room for me with employee 225, 1, 2,
0, 5 if my leave balance is more than 3 days with following details and then I provide
the hotel booking details.
Now let me just go and run this and now you can see it has given me a response.
So, it is saying that it has booked this hotel room with booking ID C2.
Now, if we just go and look at the trace, let me just click on show trace, but before
we look at the trace, let us see the tools that we are using.
So, this is my microcool AI agent and here is the tool 1, so API call hotel booking
and then tool 2, API call leave balance and now if I just look at this trace 1 and
scroll down and you will see that it has used both these tools and you can see here
it has used the tool 2, API call leave balance to get the leave balance and as we had
seen in the couple of lectures back, it is basically retrieving this data from leave balance
table.
And now if I just go to the trace steps and let me just scroll down here and here it
showing it invoked action group name tool 2, API call leave balance which we had seen here
tool 2, API call leave balance.
Now, if we just go to trace step 2 and if I just scroll down, you will see here it
showing action group name tool 1, API call hotel booking and slash book hotel room, so this
is basically this tool 1 that it has used to create the hotel booking and we have seen
couple of lectures back where this hotel booking room table where it will generate the booking
ID and store all the user details, so in summary this is how you can create multiple
tools and then integrate them with the AI agents and we are going to develop all of these
in more detail in the later sections.
For now, this is pretty much it from this lecture, I hope you liked this lecture, thank